[
    {
        "qid": 478481,
        "question": "Patient is a 13 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option3": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option4": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "67%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1152656,
        "question": "Patient is a 50 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or feels palpitations.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 212278,
        "question": "Patient is a 74 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has recently had a loss of appetite or gets full more quickly than usual.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.",
        "option1": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option2": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option3": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "71%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 759301,
        "question": "Patient is a 53 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the thyroid cartilage, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option3": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option4": "Unstable angina",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "51%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 600060,
        "question": "Patient is a 15 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option2": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option3": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "50%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 748317,
        "question": "Patient is a 65 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has recently experienced a loss of appetite or gets full more quickly than usual.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.",
        "option1": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option2": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option3": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "89%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 642577,
        "question": "Patient is a 34 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, thyroid cartilage, palate, and pharynx.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option2": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option3": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option4": "Unstable angina",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "58%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 600464,
        "question": "Patient is a 62 year old female.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels that muscle spasms or soreness in their neck are keeping them from turning their head to one side.<br>- The patient suddenly has difficulty or an inability to open their mouth or experiences jaw pain when opening it.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Myocarditis",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "91%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 539438,
        "question": "Patient is a 56 year old female.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.",
        "option1": "HIV (initial infection)",
        "option2": "Myocarditis",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "81%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 513585,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old female.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.<br>- The patient has symptoms that are increased with physical exertion but alleviated with rest.",
        "option1": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option2": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 530523,
        "question": "Patient is a 63 year old female.<br>- The patient's nose or the back of their throat is itchy.<br>- The patient has severe itching in one or both eyes.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Allergic sinusitis",
        "option2": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option3": "Cluster headache",
        "option4": "Acute otitis media",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "62%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 593484,
        "question": "Patient is a 26 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of their head.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 7 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Bronchitis",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Chagas",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 754482,
        "question": "Patient is a 49 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, palate, and under the jaw.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 9 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 9 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option2": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option3": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option4": "Unstable angina",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "74%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 154478,
        "question": "Patient is a 10 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain on the left side of the chest and in the pharynx.<br>- The patient's pain is at an intensity of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option2": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "91%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 983869,
        "question": "Patient is a 5 year old female.<br>- The patient has had significantly increased sweating.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heavy.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of the head.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.",
        "option1": "Bronchitis",
        "option2": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "74%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]